Hello everyone!
This is Minami, everyone!
My name is Sakura Endo!
Today I'm going to buy old clothes!
Yay!
This is my first visit to Koenji.
I said I wanted to go to a vintage clothing store.
I said I wanted to bring Saku with me.
I'm so glad!
He invited me!
I invited him! I brought him along.
I'm not much of a vintage clothing guy.
I've always wanted to come to Koenji.
I thought this would be a good opportunity to see it in a relaxed atmosphere.
Saku and I are going to make the rounds!
Yes!
It's cold!
The weather is really nice.
Yes, the weather is great!
Look at these shopping streets!
Wow, wow, wow!
It's so nice!
So many clothes!
It's like this, so old!
It's so old!
It's just a walk in the park today.
No, it's not.
I like walking around.
I'm glad you're here, because I really wanted you to come sometime.
I really want you to come.
Will you do it?
Yes, I would.
I'd love to, but you'll have to ask me.
I'll definitely ask you out.
Let's go somewhere.
What?
Where?
Let's go away.
Away.
Sure, sure.
But maybe a walk with Saku...
There are a lot of people who like to see you walking alone.
No, that's not true.
That's why they follow behind him.
He's going all the time.
I keep saying that.
Someday I'll follow you from behind.
That sounds interesting.
Sounds fun.
There it is.
Where?
Here.
What?
Amazing!
Wow!
Maybe only people who know how to get in.
This is where the tough guys go.
First house.
Right here, at the end of the stairs.
Wow.
But I would've liked to have gone here, if it was a restaurant.
Oh, really?
Yes, it's called "Jikaroku".
I'll go to the first one.
Excuse me.
Excuse me for interrupting.
He's here.
They're here.
Oh, my God.
Let's take a look.
He's so cute.
Can you grab my shoes?
I want a jacket.
It's so cute.
I usually wear a lot of men's clothes.
Yes, I have an image of you.
Yes, I like men's clothes.
You definitely like men's clothes at thrift stores like this.
I absolutely love it!
So cute!
Matching faces
Stylish
Are you sure?
It's really not good!
Is this original or not?
It's the original.
Of course it is.
I love public baths so much!
I tried it on.
It's so cute!
I love baths, too.
Are these sweatshirts original, too?
Yes, they're all original to the bath.
It's so cute and neat!
I've done it before.
I've never had it done.
I haven't either.
You're cute.
You're so cute!
Why don't you sit down?
You look cute.
You wear sweatshirts and long T-shirts more than T-shirts, don't you?
I see.
Really? But sweatshirts are cute.
Sweatshirts are so cute!
It's cute!
I'll go for this one.
I'll go with "ready".
I'll go with "well-dressed".
What color do you like?
Which one is it?
You always go for black, gray, and white, right?
That's right.
What should I do?
I'm going to say "Mizuri".
It's not cute.
But I'm sure it's cute.
It's so cute!
I think it's really cute.
It's not too bad.
I think I'll go with orange.
It's nice.
Isn't this pattit orange cute?
Too flashy!
It looks good on you.
Flashy, flashy, flashy.
It's going to be a flashy duo, but it's okay.
Orange and green?
Much more flashy.
Very flashy.
Yeah, but you know what?
I'll buy whatever color I like.
I like the colors.
I like the color.
Try it on.
And this one.
It's a great size, isn't it?
It's a good size. You can wear it a lot.
It's so cute!
We'll stand out at rehearsals and stuff.
Yes, we'll stand out.
I'm so glad. Let's decide on this one first.
Let's make this our first rule.
Like this.
We rehearse a lot.
So we'll wear these dowbots.
It's cute.
I want a jacket.
It's got a lot of punch.
I'd look terrible in one of these.
I'm sure I could pull it off.
It's cute.
This is the one you're painting.
Gold jersey?
Oh, my God.
That's my custom-made jersey.
I'm sure you'll never wear it again.
What?
What? That's cute.
I want the jacket.
What? I don't know which one's hotter.
Hey, you can keep filming me here.
It's hard to get a shot.
It's hard, isn't it? It's hard.
Oh, my God, you're so cute.
Calvin Klein.
Well, let's see if I can recommend some jackets.
Do you have any cool jackets?
A cool jacket.
What kind?
Simple? Black?
Oh, I like this one, too. Calvin Klein.
Yes, it's cute.
It's the most tailored.
It's cute.
I'll try it on.
Can I try it on?
Here's the fitting room I brought back.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
I'll be right here.
I can do it. Quickly, let's get started. To the outside camera.
Hey, cute.
It's so cute! It's a great size!
It looks great on you. It's so cute.
How do you like it? It's a great size. It's a great size.
Is this men's?
It looks like lace.
That's what I'm talking about.
Keymari.
No, wait a minute. Let's see more.
Cute.
One candidate.
Maybe a costume. Maybe Endo's costume.
You've probably been in our house before, right?
What?
Nogizaka-san's in general.
It's Mr. Nogizaka, isn't it?
Mr. Nogizaka.
Yes, he's already called Mr. Nogizaka.
Is that right?
We're so connected.
Actually...
It's tea.
Thank you very much.
Surprise, surprise.
We're wearing it. We're wearing it.
We're wearing it.
That's great. Thank you.
I see. We're wearing it.
It's like Gomefin's. Look.
It looks like Gomefin.
It's gonna come out around here.
What do you think? If I wore it in private like this...
What?
I'd look different.
No, but you look good.
No, no.
You haven't changed.
It's always been the same.
This is surprising.
I just...
Try it on.
Maybe it'll give you a little more speed.
See? I knew it!
It's speedy. It's speedy.
Let's try it on.
Wait a minute.
Cute.
Ta-da!
It's cute. You're showing off your speed.
Is it?
Surprisingly so.
I don't know, it's just... It's not that flashy.
It's not too flashy? A lot of women are wearing it.
It's just for models and overseas.
I think it's popular right now.
I see.
It's cool.
It's really cool.
What about everyday clothes?
Normal clothes. I get nervous.
I'm a little nervous.
It looks good on you.
I'm glad.
Everything looks good on you.
But it's cute.
It's so cute.
Thank you very much.
It's precious.
Everything looks good on you.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I like to get opinions from all kinds of people.
When I went to Fukuoka last year...
I went to Fukuoka last year.
In Fukuoka?
Yes, in Fukuoka.
So cool!
It's so cute!
The size is perfect.
It looks good on you.
Would you like to try on your favorite outfit?
It could be a challenge.
This color, this look. No, but... maybe that jacket.
I don't know if it's comfortable.
Maybe I should try something a little more challenging. This one's really cute.
It's called "fade".
High-end brands do this on purpose.
It's cute. It's cool. This is cute.
It's cute.
This one? I don't know.
I think it's good. I'm torn. I'm torn.
It's really cool.
It's cute. I think I'll go with this one.
I'll go with this one.
Decided. Decided.
So cute! So cute!
It's so cute.
Actually, there's an awful lot of clothes up there.
I'll just grab a few things from there.
Cute!
Bloom... another speedy one.
Here it is. It was for Mr. Endo.
Maybe I'll try it on.
You're a speedster, aren't you, Saku?
Thank you.
The back's amazing.
Really?
That's speed!
No face?
It doesn't look like a face.
But the color is cute.
It's so cute!
Oh, there's a pink one.
Cute. Has the color changed?
Yes, but it's so cute!
It's cute.
Isn't it super cute?
The back is amazing. The back is amazing.
Tiger.
He's got a tiger on his back.
But you look so cool in it.
Oh, my God, he's so cute!
I could totally wear that.
Really? Does he look like he'd wear it?
I think I'd wear it.
Really?
But yes, it's a cute design.
It's so cool.
Isn't it cool?
When you wear Sakwa, you look kind of...
It makes you look nice.
If I wore it, I'd probably look like I was making some kind of boo-boo.
But you're right, the color is...
It's so cute!
I like it.
It's hard to decide.
Let's try on the shakashaka.
Let's try on the Shakashaka.
It's cute.
Let's see how it looks.
What's up?
So cute!
Why are you smiling?
It's cute.
It's the perfect size.
I heard it's only sold overseas.
It's not sold in Japan.
If you say so.
If you say so...
It looks great on you.
There's a pocket on the side, right?
Yes, it does.
I heard it's only sold overseas.
Not in Japan.
It's got to be mine, right?
Yes, it does.
I think so.
They don't have them over here.
Wow, if you say so.
But it's cute.
That's so cute.
We've decided.
I guess it's decided.
How about this one?
How about that one?
You really like it, don't you?
I like it more than I thought I would.
It's not too punchy.
And it's not something I would normally buy.
You're right, you're right.
Once you meet it, it's just...
I can't help but think
If they're both gone...
Oh, no.
Next time
I'm wearing a jacket, too.
Thank you very much.
This is a new fence.
I'll certainly take good care of it.
Wear it.
I will.
I'll wear it to the field.
Thank you for coming.
That makes me happy.
There you go!
I'm standing up.
I'm wearing it.
I bought matching ones for both of us.
It's so cute!
So cute!
I'm going to keep looking for vintage clothes at this rate!
Let's go!
How cute is it?
Isn't it exciting?
I'm probably able to wear it now when I'm in shooting mode.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to wear it once I'm in private mode.
I'm a little embarrassed, aren't I?
I'll definitely wear it to the shoot.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a speedo today.
It's speed today.
It's speed.
Here we are.
Good morning.
We're at the next store.
This is the white one.
This is the worst angle.
I'll go this way.
I'm looking forward to it.
Excuse me.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Wow.
It's so cute.
It's stylish.
But it looks like Umezawa-san.
I think I like it here, too.
There's so much feminine stuff here.
Oh, it's nice.
It's so cute!
I only like the ones that you can wear over it.
It's cute.
Sleeveless.
It's kind of sexy, isn't it?
Yeah, it's sexy... in a grown-up kind of way.
Wow, it's so sparkly.
It stings my shoulders.
It's you, isn't it, Ms. Manatsu?
I thought so.
I thought it was Manatsu.
I knew you'd come out with "my shoulders are stinging," Manatsu!
Shakashaka shakashaka.
There's denim, too.
Cute.
How did you buy the denim earlier?
I don't really have denim in my size.
When I buy them myself, they're usually too big in the waist.
So I do it myself.
You stuff them?
I stuff them with safety pins.
Oh, they're so cute!
These are so cute.
Buddidos.
Oh, these are cute, too.
Maybe this one. Wow, they'd look good with these.
Even if you wear it with a regular T-shirt, it's so cool because it's speedy.
Oh, man, these are cute. These are cute, too.
These pants are cute. They'll definitely be a big hit.
These pants will definitely be a big hit.
I'm definitely going to be wearing these pants.
I'm gonna wait for the speed.
I'll wait for the camera.
Okay, I'll get it.
Hmm. What? Oh, my God! Isn't she pretty?
It's cute!
It's denim on the inside, so, you know...
I'm going for something a little, you know, healthier.
What?
Too cool!
These pants are amazing...would you comment if they were around here at the waist?
I'll give it a try.
Okay, yeah.
I could probably fit one more person in there.
Oh, no, they're so big!
But the squishiness is so cute.
Yeah, it's cute.
I think it's cute how the money comes out and goes in an array.
It's an unusual pants. It has a side line and blue pockets.
They don't go together very well.
Yeah.
You're in!
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yay!
Oh, it's so nice.
This is awesome!
I knew it! It looks great on you!
Oh, and this one, too.
They're back.
Here it is!
Great purchase!
I'm so glad.
I feel great.
I got something really nice.
What?
What's this?
But you can buy a kimono.
Hey, this is so cute.
Are they cute?
It's cute.
It's pretty cute.
Here, take this one.
Oh, my God.
Just try it on.
You don't mind?
Then...
By all means, of course.
Have fun.
So cute!
This is so cute.
I'm wearing it with the first pair of pants I ever bought.
I think I'm thinking of the pants ones.
I see.
I'm sure it's because of the split here.
Here we go.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Shhh!
You're so cute.
Shaan, how do you like it?
It's lovely.
It's cute.
Is this another pants remake?
Cute.
It's cute.
It goes with the speedo.
It's surprisingly good for speed.
I like it.
It's cute.
It's so cute.
It's a yujudean, isn't it?
I usually fall asleep.
I'm so lost.
I'm so confused.
What should we do?
What should I do?
Wow, I like it.
I love it.
The back's cute, too.
I don't know...
I'm not sure, Saku, what are you going to do?
It's called meeting someone, right?
It's an encounter.
Should I buy it?
I think it's a good idea.
It's a big deal.
It looks really good on you.
Honestly, it looks great on you.
I'll buy it.
Thank you so much.
It's cute.
Done.
It looks good on you.
You did it.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to go change.
Have a good day.
I'll get one of these too.
Look how similar they are.
It really is.
Yes, these are nighties.
Oh, please.
That was too quick, wasn't it?
It was too quick, wasn't it?
It was too quick.
Nicky.
JCB.
It was a commercial, wasn't it?
I bought it.
Here it is.
It's here.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We're...
They're adding new colors all the time.
It's true.
More and more and more.
I'm so happy.
But it's really fun to shop!
It's fun!
I'm up to speed.
Yeah, I know.
But you're used to it now, right?
You're comfortable with it?
Still embarrassed?
But now...
I don't know.
Hey.
Here we are.
I'm here.
We're here?
The grocery store.
What?
It's kind of a nice street.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
This is some nice tableware.
Yes, ma'am.
That's nice.
I love tableware.
You cook, right?
Yes, I do.
Look at this.
I've got it.
Mr. Shih.
Mr. Shih's chopstick rest.
Lilia.
Lilia, are you watching?
Mr. Shih's chopstick rest.
I put them on.
It's cute.
A mug.
Oh, it's so cute.
It's cute.
A wooden mug.
It looks like it could be a lot of things.
A mug artist.
Oh, my gosh!
Selfish house
It's there, isn't it?
Yes, it's there.
And there's a tree.
There's a lot of trees.
A frying pan?
Me...
I want a silo.
Heh.
Oh, wow.
It's so cool that you can make it.
But a rice cooker...
It's really, really easy.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You just put them in and put the lid on.
And put a lid on it.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Tea is good.
Tea's good, too.
It's nice.
It's pretty.
Is that tea?
Oh, yeah.
I want to take this on a picnic.
When I was in high school.
This was my lunch box.
Oh, my God.
It fits perfectly.
That's amazing.
I see.
I adore your lunch box.
I think mine was some kind of character thing.
So cute!
A two-tiered bento.
Cute!
salt of every day
I made a mistake
Then I'll buy the sale.
What's this?
You can use the lid.
I'm so loud. I'm so loud.
I wish you'd be quiet.
Oh, this is so cool.
I think I'll go with this one.
What do you think?
This one.
Oh!
I think we've decided.
I'll make a lot of steamed vegetables with this.
Hey, it's nice.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much!
I bought it!
The park temple vintage clothing walk is over!
Yes!
Ta-da!
I bought it!
And I'm wearing it now!
How did you like it? My first park temple!
It was a lot of fun!
It was so much fun!
I got to go to a vintage clothing store that I don't get to go to often.
I got to go to a vintage clothing store
We even bought some speedos that we wouldn't normally buy!
Speedo looks good on you too!
I'm used to it now.
I'm used to it.
Yes, I'm getting used to it.
I tried my best to wear it in private.
Yes.
Yes, I did.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, sir.
I'll wear more items and try to wear them more.
Let's wear it.
Yes, I'll wear it.
We got matching items, too.
You got it, didn't you?
Put it on.
Yes.
Somewhere...
Let's put it on.
Mmm-hmm.
Let's wear it somewhere together.
Let's wear it together.
I'll say yes.
I look forward to working with you.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
See you next time somewhere!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching!